avxhm.se 2019-05-19

# Privacy Policy

**

Privacy Statement

**  
**Information We May Collect**  
If you sign up for our email newsletter, we will collect your email address. If you create an account, we will ask for some personal information, such as a valid email address and a password, which is used to help protect your account from unauthorized access. 

**How we use Cookies**  
Cookies are very small text files that are stored on your computer when you visit some websites. We use cookies to help identify your computer so we can tailor your user experience. You can disable any cookies already stored on your computer, but these may stop our website from functioning properly. 

**The following is strictly necessary in the operation of our website.**  

This Website will remember that you are logged in and that your session is secure. You need to be logged in to use some features of our website. The following are not Strictly Necessary, but are required to provide you with the best user experience and also to tell us which pages you find most interesting (anonymously).

 **Functional Cookies**  

This Website will track the pages you visits via Google Analytics and similar tools. 

**Targeting Cookies**  

This Website will allow you to share pages with social networks such as Facebook (If available)

 **Disclosure of Information**  

We may share aggregated, non-personally identifiable information about you with third parties. This information is anonymous, statistical information that reflects usage of this website and does not include your Personal Information. We may use your email address to send messages relating to our website, from which you will have the ability to opt-out. 

**Modifying Your Information**  

You may log in to your account at any time to modify the information you provided when you created it. You may unsubscribe from any emails using the link provided in the email. 

**Modification of Privacy Policy**  

AvaxHome reserves the right, at any time, to modify, alter or update the Privacy Policy and you agree to be bound by such modifications, alterations or updates.
